all right this here is my first squat
attempt this is 364 lbs
attemp and this was really
easy I'm
6'4 so um I've always had a pretty big
forward Lane when I
squat I can stay upright but I'm weaker
so
uh that came up pretty easy so I decided
to jump to
402 402 was what I
wanted and
uh this recording is a little zoomed in
I had to get random people to help me
with this so um this is 402 and it was
pretty hard but I figured I probably had
another 10 lb or so in me so I made a
jump to
413 so this here is 4 13 and this was
pretty tough uh probably had a couple
more pounds in me maybe but this was
pretty close to my one rep max so it was
a very good call so I ended up going
uh see big sticky point
there so ended up going three for three
with my squats was very happy with that
okay moving on to bench press um first
up is
276 and this felt so light I felt like I
could have gotten like 10 reps with it
um I didn't even get a hand off on this
one um I bench with a big El with pretty
big flare I don't keep my elbows tucked
as much as most people but I'm strongest
that way and I've got muscular pecs so I
I try to use them uh plus it actually
feels better on my shoulders that way
okay here is 303 this is what I was
hoping for and it came up pretty
easy as you can see so then I thought
maybe I can hit
314 so I jumped to
314 I was a little worried that I
wouldn't get this cuz this I hadn't done
this in training well I had done this in
training but I I didn't pause at all was
kind of a bounce off my chest but they
were given fast commands really fast
press commands so that was nice so I
ended up with 314 going 3 for three on
the bench very happy with that and now
moving on to the deadlift this here is
551 my
opener and I'm experimented with a semi
Sumo stance I don't know what I think of
this a narrow
Sumo that flew up uh the lockout did so
then I I wanted to get
600 uh so next next up is
601 I've never done this the most I've
ever done done is
585 which I did 11 days ago I did
585 um so I I was pretty confident I
would get this but wasn't quite sure and
this was pretty
challenging but uh I still feel like I
had more in
me so I decided to move uh up to 612 for
my final attempt and I thought I had 11
more pounds in Me based on how I moved
one but as you can see I I failed at 6
612 again
I usually I'm stronger at my lockout
with conventional with sumo I'm stronger
off the floor but this is kind of a
narrow Sumo is
stance might go back to one or the other
but this is an odd place for me to fail
it was so hard getting off the ground I
get it right above my knees and then
usually I can push my hips forward but I
couldn't do it there anyway ended up
with a 1328 total 413 squat 314 bench
601 deadlift